
up to date, audited 2128 packages in 2m

287 packages are looking for funding
  run `npm fund` for details

136 vulnerabilities (26 low, 71 moderate, 38 high, 1 critical)

To address issues that do not require attention, run:
  npm audit fix

To address all issues possible (including breaking changes), run:
  npm audit fix --force

Some issues need review, and may require choosing
a different dependency.

Run `npm audit` for details.
